[Previously]
From now on,
we'll have nothing to do with each other.
Even if you die in front of me,
I won't save you.
Right now, I am the only heir to Thanavej.
So, get ready, scram,
and go somewhere else.
I want you to work with me
to deal with Pheem.
You're the one who killed my mom!
Dad!
[The Wicked Game]
-Dad!
Dad!
Dad...
Dad.
-Hang in there.
-Dad!
Dad!
Dad...
-Dad.
Hang in there.
Dad...
Dad!
Chet...
Dad.
Because of you...
No...
Mr. Chet didn't shoot Mr. Thanet.
It was Mr. Pheem who shot Mr. Thanet.
Mr. Chet just came to help.
I didn't do it.
You did.
You did shoot Mr. Thanet.
Don't you frame Mr. Pheem!
Run. Run now...
-Mr. Pheem!
-Just go...
Run!
Leave here...
Go, Mr. Pheem!
Run!
Mr. Pheem, get going!
Mr. Pheem!
Dad, Dad!
Call an ambulance!
I'm asking you to get an ambulance!
Chairman!
Anyone out there?
Is it the hospital?
Send an ambulance
to Mr. Thanet's home now.
Right now!
Hey! Where are you?
Where are you? Come back now!
Mr. Thanet...
Mr. Danai, don't worry.
Ms. Risa will take care of the rest.
Pheem.
Risa.
Help Dad. He got shot.
Don't worry. I'll get him an ambulance.
There will be another car
to transport your dead body.
Ah!
Don't bother to run.
You can't get away no matter what.
-Than!
-Pheem, get on my motorbike!
Go after them!
-Pheem shot Dad and Danai.
-Yes!
Dad, Dad...
Dad.
Dad...
I'm so sorry.
Please help my dad.
Pheem.
Pheem, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Take some rest, so you can recover.
Thank you.
Than,
thank you.
200 joules, defibrillation.
I'll step back. So will you.
Everyone, step back.
Clear!
[Emergency Room]
Dad...
Still no heartbeat.
Continue with the defibrillation.
I'll step back. So will you.
Everyone, step back.
Clear!
How did it go?
We tried our best.
The chairman already passed away.
What are you saying?
This can't be true.
This can't be true! It can't be true!
This can't be true!
It can't be true! Dad!
Dad...
Hey.
Than, turn on the TV now.
What happened?
This is breaking news
in the public health sector.
Thanavej Hospital just announced
the passing of its chairman,
Mr. Thanet Yotsinphaisan.
The initial statement
doesn't specify
the exact cause of death.
It'll probably take some time
for his family to process the bad news.
It's okay.
It's okay, kid.
Alright.
Coming right up.
Noodle soup with chicken thighs.
Rice vermicelli with soup and pig's blood.
Enjoy.
Dad.
Oh. Somsong!
What is it?
Come out to collect the clothes.
Looks like there will be heavy rain today.
Huh?
What's that about?
-Heavy rain? The sun is shining.
-Come here to meet this big shot.
Here, look. What a "big shot."
Whoa! Heavy rain it is!
Oh, hello, my son!
Oh. This is just over the top.
I came home. That's all.
You didn't reply to my Line messages.
You only said to me,
"It's Monday. Good morning."
Didn't I tell you to call me
if anything came up?
Sometimes Line notifications don't pop up.
-How have you been?
-Perfectly fine. I just missed you a lot.
Uh, Ms. Somsong.
-Ms. Somsong.
-Yes?
Holler when you're done with this.
-Oh. Look who's mad.
-You grumpy old man.
I was just away for a while...
Do you still remember you father?
Of course. You're my one and only.
Seems you're still tough and strong.
Hello.
-Hello.
Ah.
He's Pheem, a friend of mine.
-Is that so, Son?
-He'd like to stay with us for some time.
Oh, welcome.
Ah. I'm hungry.
-Oh, you're hungry.
-Mom.
Come here.
Do you need help?
You can sleep here, right?
Thank you, Than.
No "thank you" is needed between us.
I'm helping you simply because I want to
bring the killer of Mr. Thanet to justice.
If that's what you think,
why not turn me over to Risa?
Then you could just find a way
to deal with that.
I brought you here
only to protect the witness.
Once I get enough circumstantial evidence,
I'll handle the case as the law says,
with no personal feelings involved.
I've taken care of
the CCTV footage, Mr. Chet.
Nobody will know what happened that day.
It was me.
I know it was me who shot Dad.
I caused his death.
I caused my own father's death!
Mr. Chet, Mr. Chet.
All that happened was an accident.
I know...
you didn't mean to shoot Mr. Thanet.
That was not your fault.
It really wasn't.
Dad died because of Pheem.
Here's the true story, Chet.
Pheem and Dad got into a fight,
because Dad asked you to come back
and take over the hospital.
Pheem was so angry that he lost his mind.
He then shot Dad.
I'll testify for you.
How strange.
Dad, though you never cared about me,
I do miss you now.
Dad, you really shouldn't have died.
You should've lived
to see your daughter,
who you always considered worthless,
take control of Thanavej
and destroy your two dearest sons.
How is it? Do you find it acceptable,
Aunt Somsong's cooking?
Hey.
What do you mean by that?
"Do you find Aunt Somsong's cooking
acceptable?" What does that mean?
It means your cooking is great.
Hmm?
I was just asking if he found it
good or very good.
Oh, Dad.
You were whining to me just now,
saying that since Mom took over
the cooking,
the customers have all complained
the food being too salty.
Hem! Hem! Hem! You little punk!
It's not my fault,
nor because I like salty food.
Get the facts straight.
Pheem, what do you think? Is it good?
Yes.
Hmm. See? He told the truth.
Only he is worth making friends with.
Uh.
By the way,
-how did you two meet?
-Yeah.
Pheem,
how did you become Than's close friend?
We're not close friends, Mom.
We just met yesterday.
-Oh.
-Huh?
Well...
Um...
Actually, it's been a while
since Than and I met.
But we're not very close.
I happen to have run into trouble lately,
so Than helped me find a place to stay.
Auntie,
how may I help?
Oh, no need, kid. I can do it myself.
Go get some rest. Weren't you injured?
Auntie, you not only cook for me,
but also give me a place to stay.
I must do something for you,
or I'll feel awful.
Uh... Then wipe the dishes for me, kid.
-Oh.
-Right over there, kid.
-They've been washed.
-Okay.
Hmm.
Now, the work can be finished earlier.
Well...
Has this restaurant
been in business for a long time?
There are so many customers.
Seems your food's selling well.
We did a better job back in Bangkok.
Our restaurant was full of customers.
Sometimes I even had to make
two pots of soup a day.
-Two pots?
-Yes.
Well...
After that misfortune befell Than,
we had to move here.
You mean Than's dismissal
from the police force?
Yes.
Everyone in your family
must have had a hard time back then.
Oh, I was fine.
But Than was really depressed for a while.
He's been quite ambitious
since childhood.
He dreamed to be a cop, to help others,
and to catch bad people.
However, in the end,
he was framed for taking bribes
and became a bad guy in others' eyes.
But recently, he told me
someone offered to help him
prove his innocence,
so he could get back to being a cop.
I'm truly happy for him,
not just because he can finally
get rid of the accusation,
but also because my child can do
what he enjoys—that's my hope for him.
I want to see my child happy again.
Oh, that silly son of mine.
What's up?
Than...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I'm sorry I failed to help you
get back to being a cop,
even though I could've made it happen.
I didn't realize what I did
would hurt you so much.
Maybe this is all for the best.
At least I've found out
how the world would treat someone like me.
Wait, Than.
Than, don't be like this.
You're already great the way you are.
You know?
Don't let someone like me change you.
I'm the one who needs to change.
It's too late, Pheem.
We have nothing more to say to each other.
Let's end it here.
[Thanavej Hospital]
Chet hasn't been feeling well these days.
I'll attend tomorrow's board meeting
on his behalf.
Oh, okay. Bye.
Mr. Chet is mentally unstable now.
He can't do anything.
Why don't you just
take the reigns of Thanavej?
Because Chet is still useful
to us at the moment.
Soon,
we'll get rid of him and Pheem for good.
But now we still don't know
where Mr Pheem is.
That's right. We need to lure him out.
Come on, Dad.
Oh, you're up too.
♪ What food does a pretty lady like you
kindly provide monks with? ♪
♪ Your good deeds make you the beautiful,
charming and adorable lady you are ♪
♪ You must've offered lilies
to the Buddha, so he gave you fair skin♪
What's the next line, Son?
Your dad isn't helping.
"Your eyes are like stars."
♪ Add some basmati rice to make it look
more beautiful and exquisite ♪
At first, I thought you were good.
But as it turns out,
you're still as stupid as your mother.
Ah! Ah...
Oh.
Pheem, Pheem!
Come on. Sing with us!
-Come now!
-Sing with us, kid.
I'm good, Uncle.
I'm not good at singing anyway.
Uh... I happen to be having a headache.
See you later.
Hey!
Dad, here you are. A drink.
Okay.
Why did Pheem...
Is he sick?
Has he taken medicine yet?
I don't know.
Oh.
What's the matter, Son?
Why are you sitting here, acting cool?
Dad,
can I ask you a question?
Ask away.
If one day,
I'm deeply in love with someone
who has lied to me and broken my heart,
what will you do in my position, Dad?
will you stay with this person?
-Me?
-Yes.
Will I stay and continue
to pretend I'm dumb?
If someone lies to me like that,
I'll split up with this person.
Well...
But he said he knew he did wrong, Dad.
However, deep down, I'm worried
that the same thing may happen again.
Hmm...
The decision is all yours.
If you still can't accept it,
it won't be necessary to go back to him.
Just stay true to yourself, to your heart,
and to your feelings.
But if...
you find him forgivable
and want to go back to him,
you'll have to first believe
that you have truly forgiven him.
Thanks, Dad.
You're actually talking about...
Pheem, right?
What?
No, Dad.
I'm drunk.
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
[The heir to the hospital
is still missing]
[Investigation shows he's likely related
to his father's death]
Than, this is a serious issue.
Someone died, Son.
Mom, calm down.
Pheem has nothing to do with this.
Are you sure?
Yes, Dad.
Now, I'm having Phaen investigate
this matter.
Dad, mom, just calm down.
Trust me.
Okay.
Nothing bad will happen.
Then...
Are you sure you're safe?
Yes.
Oh, don't worry.
Nothing will happen to me.
Are you sure, Son?
Pheem.
Are you not feeling well?
My mom sent me to ask you.
Pheem?
Than,
I'm terribly sorry
for constantly causing trouble
to you and your family.
Thank you for everything
you've done for me.
Thank you for helping me,
though you didn't have to.
I shouldn't be here anymore.
I shouldn't let you and your parents fear
because of me.
I know I'm the problem.
From now on, I won't let anyone
get in trouble again because of me.
Please give my apologies to your parents.
Sorry for unsettling their minds.
I'm grateful for all the kindness
I received from you.
Thanks to you, I learned
what a loving family is really like.
Take good care of yourself.
Pheem.
What's up, Boss?
Hello, Than.
I heard Risa's people
are looking for Pheem.
Pheem and you had better be careful.
Or just hide somewhere for now.
50.
Each is 50.
This is also 50.
-What about this?
-It's a can. Vintage style.
You want a book?
[Songthaew Routes]
Excuse me, sir.
Have you seen the person in this photo
passing by?
No.
Excuse me, sir.
Have you seen this person passing by?
Not as I recall.
Thank you.
I wish you good luck.
50 baht.
-You want a book?
-Scan the code?
Excuse me.
Have you seen this person passing by?
I just started this shift not long ago.
The last Songthaew already left, sir.
[Koh Teng Hotel]
Excuse me.
Have you seen the person in this photo
passing by?
This man.
Than...
Pheem.
Why did you do this?
Why did you run away, Pheem?
Risa's people are looking for you.
What more trouble do you want to cause?
Do you know how worried I was?
Now, your entire family knows
what happened to me.
Do you expect me
to still stay at your home shamelessly?
I'd hate for your parents
to become collateral damage.
I'm going back to Thanavej
to clean up my own mess.
Are you crazy, Pheem?
You will be doomed that way.
I don't care.
I'm going back to solve my own problems,
so as to prevent you
from getting in trouble because of me.
Do you think that will put an end
to everything?
Pheem.
My life became like this because of you.
You know that?
Yes, I do.
I know this is all my fault.
I'm trying hard to solve the problem now,
aren't I?
I'm a real jerk.
I lied to you.
I planted thoughts in you and used you.
I turned your life into a complete mess
as it is now.
So, I want to sever all ties with you.
I can't bear the thought
of you suffering more.
Stop acting like you're sorry.
I won't be fooled by you again.
This is actually good.
Don't put any trust in me.
Just leave me be.
♪ I once thought what between you and me ♪
Do not go anywhere.
Do you understand?
♪ Was a meaningful love ♪
♪ I thought my heart would never ♪
♪ Ache for you ♪
♪ Today, I've finally realized ♪
♪ The love I thought I had
was just an empty promise of yours ♪
♪ My heart hurts
but I haven't learned my lesson ♪
♪ I still love you wholeheartedly ♪
♪ My heart is telling,
but I don't want to listen ♪
♪ Almost suffocated by that torture ♪
♪ You tricked me into loving you ♪
♪ Yet you left after I started trusting ♪
♪ You don't love me ♪
♪ Today my heart's completely broken ♪
♪ You left me to die alone ♪
You do understand, don't you?
Than, I love you.
♪ Today, I've finally realized ♪
♪ The love I thought I had
was just an empty promise of yours ♪
I thought last night was a dream.
Hmm?
But I think I'm the one who had a dream.
A nightmare, to be exact.
Hey.
What's that look on your face?
I'm just kidding.
Hmm.
I really think of myself
as a nightmare to you.
I used you.
I planted thoughts in you
and seriously disrupted your life.
I'm sorry, Than.
I was really hurt.
But I did some thinking.
After going through some days without you,
I finally realized
how important you are to me.
I can't live without you.
I'm truly sorry, Than.
Back then, all I wanted to do
was avenge my mother.
So, I chose Thanavej
and power.
I thought as long as I got everything,
the wounds in my heart could heal.
But that was not true.
Instead, I felt a void in my heart.
I wasn't happy at all.
I'm glad that you've thought it through.
Especially when I stayed at your house
and saw how happy you were
around your parents,
I understood that I didn't really
have a home all along.
Nobody could make me laugh.
Nobody would comfort me
when I was in pain.
Now, I know better, Than.
I know what values most to my life
is the people around me,
instead of those things
I've been pursuing.
Now is not too late, Pheem.
After dealing with Chet and Risa,
come live with me.
Okay.
I only ask you for one thing.
What is it?
Promise me that you won't run away again.
I won't.
You have my word.
I won't let you leave me again.
I see.
Pheem's family is looking for Pheem.
I've asked
Boss and Phaen for help.
Hmm.
-Here you are.
-We'll go back to address the issue
when we hear from them.
Okay.
All that matters is
that everyone's safe and sound now.
Let's eat.
There's one more thing.
Dad.
What is it now, Than?
My heart is not feeling well.
Uh...
In fact...
Pheem...
Pheem is my boyfriend.
What?
Is it true?
Oh, my son.
I was really scared.
About that,
we knew it on the day of his arrival.
I was so nervous that my heart
was pounding out of my chest.
Put it back in.
Let me place it here then.
Aww.
Come on, let's eat.
-Eat up.
-Sure.
-My son's sweetheart.
-Okay. Thank you.
Aww.
We're not sure of your roles
in this relationship yet.
Could Pheem be the one wearing the pants?
Dad! Dad, have some eggs.
Here you are. Eat up.
Have some fried eggs.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Young people all serve each other food
that way. Put some on my plate too.
You can't eat that much.
Mind the mosquitoes.
I thought you were asleep.
Keep it on. Or you might get sick.
Don't think too much.
I'm here for you.
[Thanavej Hospital]
Ms. Risa,
our people have fixed the footage.
-Don't...
-Dad!
Pheem.
This is enough to convict Pheem.
According to the autopsy report
and the information
from the coroner's office,
[Arisa Yotsinphaisan]
it's confirmed that my father
was murdered.
We're looking for witnesses
and more evidence in the preliminary stage
to identify the murderer.
But the latest proof shows
that my younger brother, Pheem,
went to our father's place
and caused quite a scene.
What happened after that is not clear yet.
Now, Pheem has gone missing.
If Mr. Pheem is watching this,
what will you say to him?
Pheem...
Pheem, come find me.
If you didn't do it,
come back to prove your innocence.
To whoever may be hiding Pheem,
please bring him to us.
I'll keep looking for you.
I'll track you and those around you down.
[One News]
I promise.
Have you watched the press conference
held by Risa?
Yes.
I think someone like Risa
must have taken care of everything.
She sounded like
she was truly concerned about Pheem.
She wouldn't be.
Risa plans to get rid of Chet and Pheem
at once.
Then she'll definitely use
everything that happened as a tool.
I think if Pheem still doesn't go back
after a while,
she'll pin all the blame on him.
All this time,
I've seen people
lingering around your apartment.
I guess she got suspicious of you,
so she sent people to lay an ambush there.
Than,
to be honest,
do you really think we can fight off
the rich and powerful?
If she tracks you down to Hua Xin,
your parents may get in danger.
Think about it.
Under no circumstances
will I let those around me get hurt.
Phaen,
can you try seeking evidence
about Mr. Thanet's death again?
See if we can use any of that.
Okay.
Hello, Mrs. Nit.
This call is about Risa, right?
I saw it.
Yes.
That message was directed to me.
She's going to eliminate
everyone who helps me.
Mrs. Nit,
can you do one last favor
for me?
What do you want me to do?
What's this about?
Hmm?
Can't I hug you?
Of course you can. Why can't you?
Hmm?
Do you remember this?
I certainly do.
It was engraved on my mind
the first time you showed it to me.
I gave you this.
Thunder Cop!
Do you always carry it with you?
Yes.
You know what?
Hmm?
This ring means a lot to me.
It keeps reminding me
that the world is not always cruel to me.
At least, I was once helped
by a little boy.
Than.
Yes?
Will you marry me?
Huh?
Are you sure?
I've never been more sure
of anything than this.
I might have done something
I shouldn't have to you...
and upset you.
But you still gave me a chance.
I don't want to lose you again, Than.
I'd like to spend the rest of my life
with you.
I want to laugh,
to cry out loud,
and to share everything with you.
I want to be with you too.
I want to be with you forever.
I also have a question for you.
Will you marry me?
I should get on one knee.
Thunder Cop,
will you marry me?
[Marriage Registration]
Have a thorough check.
[Marriage Certificate]
Here you are.
Pheem, Than, you're married now.
You shall weather through
everything together.
Always forgive
and be patient with each other, kids.
Sure.
Pheem,
this place will be your home forever.
You won't fight alone anymore.
Thank you, Mom.
I wish you happiness.
Pheem, Than told me you were alone
with no one on your side.
But from now on,
you won't be all by yourself anymore.
Should anything happen in the future,
don't just keep it to yourself,
because we're already a family.
Thank you.
Thanks, Dad, Mom.
Come here, kids.
I wish you two happiness.
Sheer and utter happiness.
May your journey together
be free of obstacles.
Thank you, Mrs. Nit.
Thank you.
Hmm.
Thank you, Mrs. Nit.
[Marriage Certificate]
Hey.
Perfect amount.
Save some of his love for me,
so he can pour it into my heart.
Drink up.
This is pure water.
Thank you.
-Ah. Come eat.
-Let's eat.
Okay.
Dad, have some crispy pork
from your favorite shop.
Here you are, Dad.
Somsong, this is delicious.
Mom, this is for you.
-Thank you.
-Fill her bowl.
Just kidding.
Hmm!
I can't believe we're truly married.
The law even allows us
to register as a couple.
Look how happy you are.
Than.
Hmm?
Thank you so much...
for giving me a second chance,
despite all those terrible things
I did to you.
Stop thinking about the past.
Let's start over, shall we?
Huh?
When Phaen comes up with a plan
to solve the problem about Thanavej,
let's hold a whole new wedding.
It has to be grand.
Only that can match your standing,
Mr. Pheem.
It doesn't have to be magnificent.
I'm happy with the one we had today.
Got it.
What's on your mind?
Nothing.
I'm just thrilled.
It's like I'm living in my dream.
I finally married my hero.
I'm truly happy, Than.
Then stay with me forever.
Don't ever run away again.
I love you, Than...
till the end of time.
Are you sure he won't wake up?
The drug's effects
will last for some time.
Pheem.
Are you sure of this?
Yes, Mrs. Nit.
I started this mess.
Of course it should be ended by me.
Pheem.
We need to talk.
Brother Chet.
[In the Next Episode]
I want to be with you forever.
But you know we can't be together
like this forever, right?
Pheem?
Mrs. Nit, I love you.
Mrs. Nit, where is Pheem?
Brother Chet, you're late.
♪ I still love you wholeheartedly ♪
[Watch the uncut version of "The Wicked Game"
on the iQIYI app and iQ.com]
♪ My heart is telling,
but I don't want to listen ♪
♪ Almost suffocated by that torture ♪
♪ You tricked me into loving you ♪
♪ Yet you left after I started trusting ♪
♪ You don't love me ♪
♪ Today my heart's completely broken ♪
♪ You left me to die alone ♪
♪ My heart hurts
but I haven't learned my lesson ♪
♪ I still love you wholeheartedly ♪
♪ My heart is telling,
but I don't want to listen ♪
♪ Almost suffocated by that torture ♪
♪ You tricked me into loving you ♪
♪ Yet you left after I started trusting ♪
♪ You don't love me ♪
♪ Today my heart's completely broken ♪
♪ You left me to die alone ♪
[The Wicked Game]